hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Krakowski and on this podcast I
help course creators coaches trainers
and mentors get more clients in their
business and make more sales now today
I'm walking around my neighborhood
actually recording this podcast trying
to turn a new format out a little bit
I've been
doing some like walking talks on my
social media but I thought you know it
might be nice to also do the same for
the podcast so if I sound like a little
bit winded it's funny because I've never
actually done this before I'm actually a
little bit nervous
doing this right now
um for the podcast because it's a
different quality things like that let
me know what you think about it I think
the content is going to be better I flow
better
I'm more conversational
um I'm less
stuck in my head and more on topic and
really flow with ideas of what I want to
share with you better yes we might have
to deal with a little bit of the wind
noise hopefully
the microphone on the
iPhone cuts it out a little bit but
beyond that yeah here we are so today I
want to talk about
um copywriting and I want to talk about
really what to focus on with your copy
in the client growth accelerator my
group coaching group we've been having a
great time we've been at the offer
Launchpad event
last week
um where we really went over what it
takes to do the five steps in your
business and what are the five steps you
you find your Niche you write your offer
copy you create a landing page offer you
launch it and then you analyze the
results and repeat that process and
and those steps if you can go through
them
as a coach as a course creator as a
mentor as a trainer you don't need to be
stuck wondering where am I going to get
clients from
you don't need to be stuck wondering
am I going to make enough money to pay
the bills because this is what we've
done consistently with all the companies
that we've worked with over the years
that have made significant
Financial gains but the the very second
step is writing your offer copy and so
in the client growth accelerator we've
got the copywriting Mastery course
which is a college level
copywriting training course
that's going to teach you how to use
artificial intelligence to write copy
and that's what we're doing right now
for all of our copy that we're we're
writing is we're using AI we're
we're using jasper.ai which is a an
incredible tool that is trained on some
of the best copywriting Frameworks some
of the best sales Frameworks to get
results to get sales and so check that
out if you're in the client growth
accelerator I think it's going to really
help you it's going to really help you
know how copy is written how to sell how
to use the written word to be able to
communicate and connect with your
prospects and connect with your clients
and be able to do that now here's one of
the most important things when you're
writing copy you want to make sure that
you
connect with the desires of your
prospect you want to make sure that
you're connecting with what the people
that you're selling to
want
this is where most people miss it with
writing their copy is they're so focused
on
what they're selling they're so focused
on the features of their product the
features of their coaching program the
features and the process and truthfully
while that stuff matters to you in the
sales process it's the very last thing
on the mind of your prospect it's
actually
gonna hurt you
if you
focus on telling people
what all the features are and that's
what a lot of amateur coaches a lot of
amateur trainers mentors do
is they lead with the features they lead
with
we have all these great things we have
all these lessons we have all this
training we have all this hours of stuff
we're going to work with you and do this
and the truth is people just want to
know
am I going to get a result
is this going to work for me
is this going to actually put money in
my bank account like for what I'm doing
that's what it does for you as a coach
as a trainer let's say that you're doing
like worship coaching people want to
know am I going to be able to write
incredible songs are they going to sound
amazing
could I get on the Billboard Chart
am I going to sound like my favorite
worship leader or let's say you're doing
recipe uh a recipe book you're helping
people write a recipe book people want
to know am I gonna be able to write a
recipe book that people are gonna
actually want to check out
or like if you're teaching
development or coding or app development
people are wondering am I gonna be able
to create my own app that's going to be
able to get on the app store that's
gonna be able to get approved that's
going to actually work out for people
and so that's what
you really want to communicate to people
is
leading them to the desired result the
desired result that your prospect has
is it's the second most important thing
the first most important thing and they
kind of piggyback off of each other
is the problem that they're having
getting there
their frustrations
when you can get to know and understand
as much as you understand your own skin
as much as you understand your own
family members like like you know what
your family members are
dealing with stuff you know when they're
not happy you know when they're sad when
you can actually understand
what pisses off and frustrates
your target client your Target customer
what angers them what makes them so
upset
what
what is stopping them what what they're
banging their head against the wall
trying to do constantly struggling
struggling when you actually understand
that
and what's preventing them from reaching
their goals
when writing your copy you want to
communicate
those two things
problems
and solutions
and then then the desired outcome
now the solution is always if you're
selling coaching training if you're
selling anything really is gonna always
be when it comes to sales
your product or service
now some people
May argue yes well there's there's
multiple roads to success and my product
could be one path listen this isn't a
time for humility
when writing copy this isn't the time
for trying to honor all roads that lead
to the result
you want your prospect to only be
focusing on you and the fact that you
are the best chance for them to succeed
that you are the best opportunity for
them to actually get the result in their
business
and so
get rid of this whole like trying to
honor other people and how amazing they
are and be humble being humble crap like
when you're selling
when you're doing your copy because
it's it's going to limit your ability
to actually connect with people to
actually connect with your prospect and
you and you might actually have people
that were meant to work with you
that will greatly benefit from your
program from your courses from your
training that you'll be repelling
because your lack of confidence and your
insecurity and your lack of belief of if
you're good enough
to actually do this
if you have what it takes if if you're
you might say well there's other people
better than me Jeremiah well yes there's
always going to be people people better
than us but when people work with you
they get a unique
connection to you they get a unique
connection
to
what you know your experience and
that's the that's the thing that they're
buying from you is that they're working
with you sure they could go and work
with a hundred other people out there
they could work with a hundred other
people
in the industry a hundred other people
that are doing what's similar to you but
they're listening to you right now and
so you don't need to worry about all
these hundreds of other people out there
you need to get it out of your head even
thinking about or focusing on your
competition a lot of people mess up when
it comes to selling when it comes to
getting customers because they're so
focused on their competition they're so
focused on all the other people out
there what other people are doing
comparing themselves to other people
comparing themselves to what they aren't
and that comes across in the language
that you say that comes across from your
copy that blatant insecurity of other
people are better than me and so I
shouldn't be confident
that belief
will limit you and keep you from being
successful and so you need to come to
the table when it comes to your
copywriting
when it comes to your sales when it
comes to your lead generation when it
comes to your marketing you need to come
to the table
with this belief that you are
the best chance that that person that's
watching you that's visiting your page
has and yes it might feel arrogant
it might feel conceited it might feel
uncomfortable for you to actually think
that highly of yourself but the level of
self-esteem self-belief and how highly
you think of yourself
determines how much money you can make
now none of us wants to be these
self-centered arrogant abusive rude
right we don't want to be that
way you're not going to be if you're
somebody who has integrity and you have
a desire not to be that way
you're not going to go too far in the
wrong direction you actually could use a
little bit of selfishness you actually
could benefit from
a little bit of
believing a little more highly about
yourself and then tooting your own horn
every once in a while when you go out
there to Market your product to Market
your service to reach your Target
customer instead of trying to say well
ah yeah yeah I know that there's all
these other people out there say listen
this is going to get you a result
this is going to get you to where you
want to be we've done it before with
other people I can help you do it as
well this is going to take you from
where you are to where you want to be
and have confidence and assuredness and
Surety inside of yourself while you're
communicating that while you're
connecting that with people to where
you're not afraid of what anybody's
going to think about you where you're
not afraid of people judging you or
misunderstanding you or or not
connecting with you because of that
you've got to break up with the fear of
other people's opinions
you've got to break up with the worry
of what other people think about you
constantly
if you want to be successful in a
business
in a course business in a coaching
the worry and fear
of other people thinking bad things
about you
will be the greatest thing that limits
you and as soon as you can rip that out
of your brain
the more successful that you will be and
you will write your sales copy you'll
communicate your sales messages you'll
attract better prospects
from that place of confidence
and this is a place where
the idea of fake it till you make it is
important because it's about mindset
it's about thinking it's about how you
think about yourself think more highly
of yourself
when you come to the table when you come
to the negotiating table when you come
to marketing putting your offers out
there getting leads getting people to
sign up with you and and stop trying to
play the the humble game stop trying to
play the the
thinking low of yourself game you it's
gonna just hurt you in the long run okay
and so with that what you want to do
then is
you are the best solution that people
have when they sign up with you believe
that I need you to believe that because
your copy is going to suck unless you
believe that
it absolutely will
it's gonna be the worst sales copy on
the planet
if you don't believe that about yourself
or if you're if you're writing copy from
an angle of trying to defend yourself
against haters defend yourself against
critics this is something that I used to
do a lot as I would try to basically
create these arguments in my sales copy
to make sure that people wouldn't think
bad about me and try to prove myself and
that only comes across as insecurity and
so if you can really cultivate
self-belief
cultivate level of self-esteem whatever
you got to do
there's a number of different ways that
we can do this there's a number of
different practices to do this is a
number of different podcast episodes
where I've talked about on how you can
do this
you don't need to be stuck
just experiencing
what you're experiencing right now
you don't need to be stuck fearing
am I going to make money are they going
to buy for me are they going to resonate
with me
and worried about are they going to
criticize me are they going to think
that I'm not good enough and then trying
to defend yourself
oftentimes we've been taught in life
that we have to defend ourselves defend
our position
make sure that people know what we mean
to not be misunderstood and that that
can be the most detrimental angle that
you can take when writing sales copy
you want to write your sales copy from
the perspective of the world's most
confident person
and sometimes you might need to put
yourself into a mind State that's
unnatural for you to do that is that if
I believed in myself more than anything
else if I believed that this is going to
help people more than anybody else how
would I communicate that or or what if I
was writing this sales letter
for the the the greatest course creator
the greatest coach on Earth and start to
believe that you are the greatest course
grader the greatest coach on Earth
when you do this
and you go and you write copy
and you communicate the problems
and the solutions that you offer you
communicate the problem that the
prospect is having reaching their goal
and you do so confidently not worried
not fearful
with some
belief with some real tangible I believe
in myself I know that I know that I know
that I know the people's lives are
benefiting from working with me that
people's lives are made better
when they come in contact with me that's
what I believe I believe that if you're
watching this podcast right now that
your life is better from engaging with
me that those that are in my client
Earth accelerator that their lives are
made better
by being a client of mine
and so whatever you got to do to believe
that in yourself is going to be worth it
for you to create your business for you
to create your coaching business
whatever you got to do
to cultivate that absolute crazy level
of self-belief is going to translate to
sales for you
and so when you write your copy more
than anything else I think it's about
even a mental state of mind one of the
things that I love to do is I'll I'll go
for a walk like I'm doing right now and
I will dictate my sales copy
I'll dictate it out
when I dictate it out it allows me to
connect better
with those that I'm working to reach
with those that I'm trying to reach
because I'm not stuck in my head because
I'm not stuck trying to over analyze how
are people going to receive this you got
to get rid of that you got to get rid of
the overthinking bug
you got to get rid of that mental
framework of needing to process through
everything in your brain I get that
maybe that's your personality that maybe
that's how you've been your whole life
I've been that way my whole life and I
had to get over it I had to break up
with that framework of operating that
framework of thinking to be able to be
The Confident person that you see me as
today
and and by doing that my business grew I
was able to sell better I'm able to
communicate better I don't have to
second guess my thoughts before I say
them and so when you come to the table
when you start
reaching your Target customer when you
start selling
and you communicate with confidence you
communicate
the problem they have why do you want to
communicate the problem because they
need to know that you understand what
they're going through
they need to know that you've that
you've been in their shoes even if you
haven't been in their shoes before they
need to at least feel like
you've been in their shoes are you at
least you have empathy for what they're
going through that you at least
understand
the struggle that they're having
and that
do you understand what their desires are
what their goals are what the solution
is that they're looking for when you can
communicate the problem that your
prospect is having
the desired solution the desired goal
you can then lead them to
the best possible solution
for them which is working with you which
is hiring you which is becoming a client
of yours which is buying your course
which is buying your program
nothing else all roads lead to your
offer
all roads lead to
working on their beliefs
helping them see you as the best chance
to work with as the best opportunity to
reach their goals
don't even put a hint of doubt in their
mind this isn't a matter of Integrity my
friends
a lot of people make this a matter of
Integrity where they're like well to be
Integris I gotta show people that
there's a thousand options out there no
you don't
no you don't and I used to think that
people have no trouble comparison
shopping on their own without your help
and so you don't need to talk people out
of working with you just because you're
trying to be honest with people just
because you're trying to be Integris
with people too many people miss out on
sales in their business because they're
trying to be
honest and Integris with people I'm not
talking about you being dishonest and
being a person with a lack of Integrity
if you follow me you know that
as you listen to me for a while you know
that
you know that I'm somebody that that
truth is the number one thing that I
care about
that living a life of Integrity
something that I care about
but sometimes we can take it to the
extreme
to where we
actually show up as a very unconfident
unbelieving person that doesn't believe
in ourselves that is essentially trying
to talk our Prospect out of working with
us because we're afraid of them saying
well there's other people out there that
are better than you how can you say that
you're the best stop worrying about that
the right person who's meant to work
with you
the right person who's meant to become
your customer
your client is going to love working
with you
that and the ones that are going to
criticize you the ones that are going to
second-guess you those haters
they're not the ones that are going to
actually purchase from you in your
business
and this is the last thing I'm going to
share with you about your copy
is
you need to focus on
who are the people that are actually
going to spend money with you in the
beginning you don't know that
so all you have to go off of is who's
actually communicating with you but a
lot of the loudest voices are the most
critical ignore the criticism ignore the
haters
ignore the people
that are coming up with reasons why they
shouldn't work with you that are trying
to talk you out of your belief
they're not your concern they're not the
people that you need to be connecting
with
the ones that you need to be connecting
with and communicating with are the ones
that are ultimately going to become
buyers and those are the ones that
everything that you say they love and
they connect with and they're
encouraging you and they're joyful and
they're happy and so when you work on
what's going on between your two ears
and you stop second guessing yourself
and you stop constantly listening to
critics you constantly stop listening to
the critic in your own brain especially
your own brain is going to be the
hardest critic you ever have to silence
and you say you know what
I'm gonna believe in myself today that
I'm a badass
I'm going to believe in myself today
that I am the best chance that people
have to work with
and you come to the table and you right
from that position in your sales copy
and you communicate
those
those solutions that you offer when you
communicate the end result outcome that
the person has that ultimate desire they
have and you demonstrate that you have
empathy and you demonstrate that by
working with you that you can give
somebody their desired result
if they trust you
they will buy from you
and that's the name of the game when it
comes to sales when it comes to sales
copy when it comes to creating your
campaigns is trust building every single
activity that we do is a trust building
exercise You're Building trust with
complete strangers people that don't
know who you are
your goal
is to connect with them
and to build that trust with them
the reason they sign up with you they're
curious about the result that you
promise but they're always going to be
skeptical they're they're they're not
going to believe you until you build
that trust with them
and so that's what your offers do and
that's why Live Events are the best
trust building exercises because when
you do a live event you're connecting
with somebody in a much closer
atmosphere in a much more their guard is
down and your guard is down and they can
see that and when you do that and you
show up as a confident person you'll
have buyers and that's what's growing
our business and that's what skilled our
business
is by doing live virtual events online
where we get people through Facebook ads
through Tick Tock ads through Twitter
ads to sign up
for Live Events we do them on Zoom and
we help people create their lead magnets
write their copy create their video ads
launch their coaching business come up
with their offers
and by doing that we're able to
demonstrate to people that hey I'm here
for you and I'm going to provide support
and that's what people want they want to
know that they're going to be supported
and that you're going to help them get
to the result they want to know that you
will be with them
every step of the way
along their Journey
now yeah obviously you can't be with
everybody 24 7. but you don't need to
defend that or explain that or explain
that over the
over the moon to people
that's why you want to write down on
your page you know you might have one
weekly call with them you might have one
coaching training I explicitly explain
that to people in my marketing
obviously don't lie to people obviously
don't
promise things that you actually can't
deliver but don't be afraid to set
boundaries and say Hey listen this is
how much I'm going to show up that's
what I'm going to provide and this is
what you're buying and
to be honest if you're selling anything
for less than a thousand dollars less
than 997 dollars you're selling yourself
short you're robbing yourself you're
stealing from your opportunities to be
able to make enough money to scale your
business to run enough ads and so you
need to start charging more in your
business
and that starts with believing in
yourself more everything every single
thing comes right back to
believing in yourself more
believing that you can do it
believing that you can accomplish every
single thing that you set out to do
and then finding people
that desire that result that you're
promising and you run ads to do that and
we run campaigns and then you sell to
those people that solution that you
offer
that my friends is how you write killer
copy that connects with people now
obviously there's a lot more to it and
we go into that in the client or the
accelerator and copywriting Mastery we
use Jasper to actually come up with some
of these words we actually use
artificial intelligence to come up with
these we use Frameworks like problem
agitate solution Ada attention interest
desire action to write copy but this is
the mental framework that you want to
get into before you're writing the sales
copy that's going to help you come
across as the most confident and the
most powerful person and ultimately make
the most amount of money in your
business which is what you want to make
and so listen
if this has helped you share this
episode with somebody we got over 189
episodes on the grow Your Life podcast
for coaches course creators trainers and
mentors and I want to help you make as
much money as possible in your business
and so if you're somebody that is a
coach is a course grader is a trainer is
a mentor follow me on social media
subscribe to this podcast plug in share
with me what are you struggling with
what are you dealing with where are you
stuck in your business and I want to
help you get unstuck great life
everybody and we'll talk soon
[Music]